McCaddon Collection of the Barnum and Bailey Circus, 1871-1907 (bulk 1895-1905): Finding Aid TC040
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Scrapbooks, 1849-1968 December 19; 25 boxes
  - Scrapbook 1A, 1865-1873; 1 box
    - Catalogue of Showmen's Stock Bills, 1870; 1 box (Box 17, Page 3)
    - Old John Robinson's Circus, advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 4)
    - History and description of Col. C. T. Ames. circus etc., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 5)
    - Bill Lake's Circus etc., advertisement/sample money order for Hemmings and Cooper's circus etc., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 6)
    - Advertisement for Erie RR/Van Amburgh and Co.'s ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 7)
    - Van Amburgh and Co.'s response to slur by J. E. Warner and Co. "Great Pacific", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 8)
    - Attack on Van Amburgh and Co. by J. E. Warner and Co., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 9)
    - Van Amburgh and Co. advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 10)
    - Hemmings, Cooper and Whitby's Menagerie and Circus, advertisement for Shoo Fly Minstrells, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 11)
    - Warner's "Great Pacific" Museum Menagerie and Circus, ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 12)
    - Great European Circus, ad, 1871, sample puzzle envelope from Robinson's Circus, 1 box (Box 17, Page 13)
    - Bill Lake's Hippo-Olympiad and Mammoth Circus 1868, ad, 1 box (Box 17, Page 14)
    - John Robinson's Circus, Courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 15)
    - Bill Lake's Circus, poster, 1865; 1 box (Box 17, Page 16)
    - editorial page mentioning Barnum's American Museum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 17-18)
    - G.W. Kirbye and Madame Kirbye, Magician, Ventriloquist, equilibrist and athletes, Handbill, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 19)
    - Rosston, Springer and Henderson's, Menagerie, Museum, Hippodrome, 1871, ad, 1 box (Box 17, Page 20)
    - Bill Lake's poster, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 21)
    - Forepaugh's Show, Courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 22)
    - Challenge from Adam Forepaugh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 23)
    - New York Circus, ad/Concert Announcement, J.A. Bailey's Minstrel and Variety Combination, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 24)
    - European Circus, Courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 25)
    - Col. C.T. Ames, Menagerie Circus, Courier, 1870; 1 box (Box 17, Page 26)
    - J.E. Warner and Co. attack on Van Amburgh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 27)
    - Charlie Noyes' Circus and Van Amburgh's Menagerie, attack on rivals and advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 28)
    - Bill Lake's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 29)
    - Adam Forepaugh's challenge to rival shows, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 30)
    - Original by Bailey of form letter accompanying comps. to clergy, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 31)
    - Comps. to Hemmings and Cooper/Robinson's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 32)
    - Notice of the auction of the late William Lake's Hippo-Olympiad and Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 33)
    - Ad for American Agriculturalist paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 33-34)
    - Van Amburgh's Circus, circular, 1870; 1 box (Box 17, Page 35)
    - Ad for the Great Golden Menagerie, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 36)
    - James Robinson's Circus, courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 37-38)
    - Bill Lake's Circus, courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 39)
    - Hemmings and Cooper's Circus, courier, 1871; 1 box (Box 17, Page 40-42)
    - Van Amburgh and Co., Mammoth Menagerie, advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 43)
    - Attack on Hemming, Cooper, and Whitby by Forepaugh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 44)
    - James Robinson's Great Circus, paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 45)
    - Van Amburgh's Circus, paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 46)
    - Hemmings and Cooper, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 47)
    - Great Eastern Menagerie, Museum, etc, 1873; 1 box (Box 17, Page 48)
    - Alphabet Book from Lake's Hippo-Olympiad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 49)
    - Forepaugh Shows, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 50)
    - Cole's Monster exhibitions, advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 51)
    - Forepaugh Shows, advertisement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 52)
    - Hemmings and Cooper, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 53)
    - James E. Cooper's Circus, courier, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 54)
    - Bill Lake's Hippo-Olympiad, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 55)
    - P.T. Barnum's Great Show, ads/Cooper's Show, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 56)
    - J.E. Cooper Shows, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 57)
    - J.E. Warner and Co. "Great Pacific" Consolidation, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 58)
    - J.E. Cooper, ad./Forepaugh Shows, ad., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 59)
    - Howes Circus ad from one of the last stands, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 60)
    - Sample tickets from Great London Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 17, Page 61)
  - Scrapbook 2: Barnum & Bailey Ltd., London, 1898-1899; 1 box
    - London News clippings regarding Barnum and Bailey establishing themselves as a British Firm, 1898; 1899; 1 box (Box 18, Page 1-39)
    - Memorandum of Association, Barnum and Bailey Ltd., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 18, Page 40)
    - Samples of allotment letters regarding purchase of ordinary shares of Barnum and Bailey Ltd., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 18, Page 41-42)
    - Sample letter of regret, returning down payment for shares of Barnum and Bailey Ltd., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 18, Page 43)
  - Scrapbook 3: Cooper & Bailey, USA and Australia Tours, 1876-1877; 1 box
    - Cooper Bailey and Co. Route Book, 1876; 1 box (Box 19, Page 1)
    - Exhibition at Honolulu en route to Australia, 1876 November 16; 1 box (Box 19, Page 2)
    - Carlo, true dog story, Galesburg, Ill., 1876 June 3; 1 box (Box 19, Page 3-4)
    - List of Circuses starting the season of, 1876; 1 box (Box 19, Page 5-7)
    - Opposition attack upon Cooper and Bailey and Co., dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 8)
    - Reply to above, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 9)
    - Programme and notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 10)
    - Auction sale of surplus animals, San Francisco, 1876 October 25 Australian theatres and populations, 1876, 1 box (Box 19, Page 11)
    - Illustrations in Sydney Punch, 1876 December; 1 box (Box 19, Page 12-13)
    - Illustrations in Sydney Punch, and opening notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 14-15)
    - Opening Press notices, Sydney, Australia and Programme, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 16)
    - New York Clipper letter from Sydney, 1877 January 27; 1 box (Box 19, Page 17)
    - Sydney Programmes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 18)
    - Melbourne opening, 1877 February 17; 1 box (Box 19, Page 19)
    - Press notices, Melbourne, Australia, 1877 February 1; 1 box (Box 19, Page 20-25)
    - Special article by "a vagabond", Melbourne, Argus, 1877 February 3; 1 box (Box 19, Page 26-28)
    - Opening Ads and notices at Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 29)
    - Victorian RR orders, Melbourne programmes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 32)
    - Up-country Press notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 33-38)
    - New York Clipper letters from Melbourne, 1877 February; 1 box (Box 19, Page 38-39)
    - South Australian Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 40-43)
    - South Australia Railway Orders, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 44)
    - Tasmania Press notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 45-50)
    - Queensland Press notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 52-55)
    - Wilson's Circus in Sydney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 57)
    - Return engagement to Sydney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 58)
    - Press notices, Handbills, programs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 64)
    - Route book Australian Tour, Season, 1876-1877; 1 box (Box 19, Page 67)
    - Dutch East Indes - License form, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 19, Page 71)
    - List of Circuses starting 1877 season, 1 box (Box 19, Page 72-73)
  - Scrapbook 4: Cooper & Bailey, Australia Tour, 1876-1878; 1 box
    - Death of Mrs. Robert Stickney, 1873; 1 box (Box 20, Page 1)
    - Cooper & Bailey at Honolulu, 1876; 1 box (Box 20, Page 1)
    - Visit of the King Honolulu, 1876; 1 box (Box 20, Page 2)
    - Opening Adv. Sydney, Australia, 1876 December; 1 box (Box 20, Page 2)
    - Press Notices Sydney, Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 4)
    - The Press Sydney, Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 5-12)
    - Boxing Day, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 13-31)
    - The Press Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 32-33)
    - The Press Up Country Victoria, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 34)
    - Special Article by The Vagabond, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 35)
    - The Press Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 36)
    - The Press Melbourne/Special Train Orders, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 37)
    - The Press Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 38-41)
    - Letters from Ministers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 42)
    - Special Train Orders. Hand Bill Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 42)
    - The Press Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 43-44)
    - The Press Adelaide, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 45)
    - The Press, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 46)
    - Unloading Elephants from Steamer, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 47)
    - The Press Up Country Victoria, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 48-62)
    - Special Train Orders South Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 63)
    - The Press South Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 64-65)
    - The Press Tasmania, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 66-74)
    - Jem Mace at Wilson's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 75)
    - The Riggs of Briggs at Sydney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 76)
    - The Press Sydney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 77-79)
    - Wilson Circus Programme, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 80)
    - Sale - Surplus Material San Francisco - Show License Honolulu, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 81)
    - Letter from Brigham Young, at Salt Lake, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 82)
    - The Press, Queensland, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 83)
    - The Death of "Carlo" & Elephant Betsey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 84)
    - Press Notices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 85)
    - 2 years Tour Chiarini's Royal Italian Circus and Receipts, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 86)
    - Cablegram from Middleton to Bailey - returning from Java, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 87)
    - Handbill - Java, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 88)
    - Programme Java, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 89)
    - Letter from W.G. Crowley, N.Y. Clipper from Honolulu, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 90)
    - Letter from The Bishop of Brisbane, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 91)
    - Programme Sydney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 92-93)
    - Programme Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 94-95)
    - Programme Adelaide, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 96)
    - Programme Syd+-ney, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 20, Page 97)
  - Scrapbook 5: Cooper & Bailey, Australia & South America Tours, &, 1877; 1878; 1 box
    - The Press Adelaide, South Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 3-4)
    - The Press New Zealand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 5-7)
    - The Press San Francisco, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 8)
    - The Press Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 9)
    - American Circus Owners & their Homes, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 10)
    - The Press Up Country Victoria, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 11)
    - The Press New Zealand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 12-14)
    - Howes Great London Show, 1876; 1 box (Box 21, Page 15)
    - The Press New Zealand, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 16-27)
    - The Press South America, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 28-29)
    - Death of "Carlo" - Elephant Dog - The Press America, 1876; 1 box (Box 21, Page 30)
    - The Press America, 1876; 1 box (Box 21, Page 31-32)
    - Press, Letter by The Bishop of Melbourne, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 33)
    - Opening San Francisco 1876 - Auction of Montgomery Queen's Circus, 1 box (Box 21, Page 34)
    - Train Orders, Victoria, Australia, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 35)
    - Letter from The Mayor Auckland, 1876; 1 box (Box 21, Page 36)
    - Programme San Francisco, 1876; 1 box (Box 21, Page 37)
    - Programme 2nd year Australia, 1878; 1 box (Box 21, Page 39)
    - Handbill Wm. Cooke's Circus - Bristol, England, 1849; 1 box (Box 21, Page 41)
    - License - Soerabaja, Java - Employees Contract, 1875; 1 box (Box 21, Page 42)
    - Programmes Peru, So. America, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 43)
    - Programmes Chiarini's Circus, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 45)
    - Programmes /South America, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 46-50)
    - Japanese Programme, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 51)
    - Route book - Australian Tour, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 53)
    - Spanish Handbills - South America, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 55)
    - Programmes South America, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 21, Page 56-57)
  - Scrapbook 6: Barnum, Bailey, & Hutchinson, Winter, 1882-1883; 1 box
    - Adam Forepaugh and Frank James (Outlaw), 1882; 1 box (Box 22, Page 1)
    - P.T. Barnum's Statement and Foreign Circus Agents, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 1)
    - Interview with W.C. Coup. Forepaugh's English Agent regarding Jumbo, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 2)
    - Letter from P.T. Baird Smithsonian Institute, 1882; 1 box (Box 22, Page 3)
    - Sale of Myer's Circus London, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 3)
    - Lily Langtry and Jumbo Sacred White Elephant, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 4-5)
    - $10,000 Beauty Suit against Forepaugh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 6)
    - Harper Bros. Publisher's Visit Winter Quarters, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 7)
    - Jumbo in Winter Quarters - Bridgeport, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 8)
    - Interview with George Arstingstall re Jumbo and Elephants, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 8)
    - J.B. Gaylord Agent in the Far East, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 9)
    - Yankee Circus in Far East and Sacred Elephants, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 10)
    - Twenty Elephants take a swim, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 11)
    - Interview with "Zazel" White Elephants in Siam, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 12)
    - Old Circus Clowns - Famous Leapers, "Just beyond the limits." Krao Hairy Girl, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 13)
    - Katie Stokes - Rider, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 14)
    - Sketch of Adam Forepaugh, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 15)
    - Attack on Circuses by Rev. T.G. Whitten. Answer by agent of Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 16)
    - Baby elephant "Bridgeport", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 17)
    - Louise Montague lawsuit, $10,000 Beauty, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 18)
    - Yankee Robinson's letter head, 1874; 1 box (Box 22, Page 21)
    - Interview with P.T. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 23)
    - Curiosities made to order, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 24)
    - A Circus in Winter Quarters, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 26-27)
    - Curiosities or Freaks - by J. R. Davis, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 29)
    - Sample Show Tickets, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 29)
    - Sample Show Tickets, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 30)
    - Elephant "Queen" and Baby, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 31)
    - Invitation to Ministers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 33)
    - Sample P.T. Barnum letter papers, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 34-35)
    - Poem to Gorilla by Dr. W.W. Ely, photo of Troglodytes Gorilla, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 36)
    - Barnum's animals in Winter Quarters. Harper's Young People, 1882 February 21; 1 box (Box 22, Page 37)
    - Sample comp. tickets, Cooper and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 38-39)
    - Form letter accompanying comps, Great London Circus, 1880; 1 box (Box 22, Page 40)
    - Sample Great London Circus letter paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 41)
    - Samples of free ticket to baby elephant show, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 42)
    - Comp. ticket to president or superintendent of schools notice of RR excursion fares, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 22, Page 43)
    - Letter to RR in regard to Great London Shows advertising, 1879; 1 box (Box 22, Page 44)
  - Scrapbook 7: Barnum & Bailey vs. Sells Bros. Opposition, 1891-1892; General (to 1935), 1 box
    - McCaddon's note explaining circumstances surrounding the articles in this book: Sells use of Charles B. Stowe to discredit Bailey and his circuses, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 1)
    - Sells Bros. ad in Town and Country journal, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 2)
    - News clippings both pro and against Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 3)
    - Anti-Bailey slurs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 4)
    - Anti-Bailey slurs. Pro Sells Bros. clippings, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 5)
    - Anti-Bailey press releases by Sells Bros. Wallace and Anderson good review of Barnum and Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 6)
    - Anti-Bailey releases (one by Stowe), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 7)
    - Anti-Bailey release. Pro & against Sells Bros. Reviews, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 8)
    - Article on the fight between circuses, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 9)
    - Pro-Sells Bros. release, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 10)
    - Two anti-Sells Bros. news clippings. Two slurs anti-Bailey released by Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 11)
    - Sells Bros. ad. Note from T. McCaddon re: paper, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 12)
    - Anti-Bailey slurs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 13)
    - Scurrilous handbills and notes from newspaper editors in support of Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 14)
    - Some anti-Bailey releases by Sells Bros. Bailey press releases in his own favor, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 15)
    - More anti-Bailey slur sheets, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 16)
    - Anti-Bailey slurs. 1 pro-Bailey statement, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 17)
    - Anti-Bailey signed by Stowe and Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 18)
    - Anti-Bailey in letter to Bailey from Stowe, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 19)
    - More anti-Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 20)
    - Bailey's notice to Australian newspaper editors, warning against Sells Bros. abuse of Barnum and Bailey's trademark "Greatest Show on Earth", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 21)
    - Letter from H.G. Barnum, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 22)
    - Full page summarizing and celebrating the "Greatest Show on Earth", dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 23)
    - Misleading playbill, suggesting the union of the two shows, Sells Bros. and Barnum & Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 24)
    - Forepaugh posters, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 25)
    - Sells Bros. "anti-monopoly" posters, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 26-28, Page 30-31)
    - Sells Bros. posters (oversize), dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 33-41)
    - Paper filled with anti-Bailey slurs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 42-46)
    - Forepaugh's Shows, notice from Copper that employees ought to refrain from responding to libelous statements, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 47)
    - Sells Bros. ads and anti-Bailey slurs, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 48)
    - Barnum and Bailey's poster alleging that Sells hiked its prices for Southern audiences, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 49)
    - Sells Bros. "Press Tips" slurs anti-Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 50-51)
    - Telegrams to Bailey from Campbell re: possibility of Sells Bros. performances and billing in the Midwest, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 52)
    - Barnum's final letter to Bailey before his death, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 53)
    - Telegrams to Bailey from McCaddon and Gardner re: Stowe's slanders, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 54-55)
    - Telegrams to Bailey from Campbell re: possibility of Sells Bros. compromise, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 56)
    - McCaddon-Bailey telegrams re: Sells Bros. backing down on slurs and compromise, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 57)
    - 1st draft of response to Stowes slurs, both vetoed by Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 58-59)
    - More anti-Bailey and pro-Sells Bros. press releases, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 60)
    - Bailey ads. Ads denouncing Sells Bros. price hike in South, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 61)
    - Sells ad for Macon, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 65)
    - More telegrams between Bailey et al. Also from Sells and Ringling Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 66-68)
    - Barnum and Bailey ads, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 68)
    - Sells Bros. ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 69-70)
    - Barnum and Bailey ad. Montgomery, Ala, 1894; 1 box (Box 23, Page 71-74)
    - Sells Bros. anti-Bailey. Bailey pro-self, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 75)
    - Pro-Bailey news reports. Sells vs. Barnum & Bailey in 150,000 suit for libel instigated by Sells, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 76-77)
    - Barnum and Bailey ad. Anti-Sells release, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 78)
    - Sells Bros. ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 79)
    - Another copy of "A Modern Iago" anti-Stowe article vetoed by Bailey, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 80)
    - Full page Barnum and Bailey ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 81)
    - Barnum and Bailey ads, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 82)
    - Ringling Bros. Texas ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 84-85)
    - Sells Bros. vs. Ringling Bros. in Texas, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 86)
    - Sells ad. Anti-Sells Bros. article, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 87)
    - X-large Barnum and Bailey poster warning against Sells Bros. corrupt practices, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 88)
    - Sells Bros. ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 89)
    - Two Sells Bros ads, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 90)
    - Ringling Bros. ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 91)
    - Sells Bros. ad, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 92)
    - Ringling Bros. ad anti-Sells Bros, dates not examined; 1 box (Box 23, Page 93)